esupermommy.com 2013-11-29

# Privacy Policy | Experience of a Super Mommy

At www.esupermommy.com, I respect your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at my site. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

Log Files  
Like most other Web site, www.esupermommy.com use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

E-mail Subscription  
If a user wishes to subscribe to my posts via e-mail (powered by Feedburner), I ask for contact information such as name and email address. It is a way to opt-out of these communications as provided.

Cookies  
My site use cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. Some of my business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, I have no access to or control over these cookies, once I have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section.

Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Advertisers  
I use outside ad companies to display ads on my site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and I do not have access to these information. I work with the ad companies: Google Adsense and infolinks. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

Links  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites that you wish to visit. I encourage my users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions regarding my privacy policy, please contact me by filling up the [contact form](http://www.esupermommy.com/contact-the-administrator/ "esupermommy contact form").

_

  * Bio
  * Latest Posts

Web administrator- Mommy Blogger. Independent Contractor. Full time mommy with two kids; very supportive to family and a loving wife. Living in a simple life. Computer Engineering Graduate. Previous works - Web Evaluator, Technical Support, Call Center agent, Collections staff, Local Store Marketing, Businesswoman, and an Internet cafe owner.

_
